A Guide to the Blackley Family Papers, 1830-2016: SC 0232
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Blackley Family Papers
1830-2016
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Blackley Family
SC 0232
13.57 cubic feet; 28 boxes, 2 flat folders
The Blackley Family Papers, 1830-2016, consists of hundreds of letters that span from 1830 to 2011; diaries; official United States, Confederate, and Texas documents; literary works; newspaper clippings; postcards; ephemera; and photographs. These papers document the related Scott, Bassett, Blackley, Hoge, Matthews, and Nix families of Texas and Staunton, Virginia.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Portions of the collection marked as restricted are inaccessible to researchers until January 1, 2035. Until the restriction is lifted, the materials will be housed in the collection control file. Additionally, an 8mm roll of film documenting Stuart Hall's 1954 May Day celebration from Series 4 is housed in freezer storage as it awaits reformatting. Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection. Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the James Madison University Special Collections library to use this collection.
Acquisition Information
Charles P. Blackley Jr. of Staunton, Virginia donated this material in various accretions throughout 2015 and 2016. On August 28, 2018, 1 half-hollinger letter box was donated by Chuck Blackley.
Other Formats Available
Digital images of nineteenth-century correspondence and papers are available upon request.
Bio/Historical Note
The Blackley Family Papers document the related Scott, Bassett, Blackley, Hoge, and Nix families of mostly Texas and Staunton, Virginia between 1830 and 2016. James Scott (1799-1856) was a Tennessee native and former Mississippi Supreme Court chief justice who married Sarah Lane (1803-1880) and settled in Anderson, Texas. James was a prominent Texas judge who was friends with Davie Crockett. While in Mississippi and Texas, James and Sarah had six children. The eldest, Elizabeth "Lizzie" (1833-1917), was born in Mississippi in 1833, Sarah "Sallie" (1843-1914), born April 9, 1843 in Texas, and one of their brothers, Garrett (1838-1862), born in 1838, contribute the most to this collection of letters.
Lizzie married William H. Neblett (1826-1871), a farmer and attorney, in 1852. He eventually left her to go fight for the Confederacy. Her domestic struggle on the home front during the Civil War is the subject of Erika L. Murr's book, A Rebel Wife in Texas: The Diary and Letters of Elizabeth Scott Neblett, 1852-1864 (2001).
In 1862, Sallie married Robert Houston "R.H." Bassett (1836-1870). R.H. went on to enlist and serve in the famed Hood's Texas Brigade from 1861 to his wounding in 1864. He worked briefly as the adjutant general to Major General John Bell. While leading the regiment, he was wounded at the Battle of Chickamauga by an artillery shell fragment that lodged in his shoulder. This would effectively end his role in the war. Following the conclusion of the conflict and his recovery from the wound, R.H. tried his hand at politics in a bid to represent Grimes County, Texas in Congress. Their first child, Robert, died tragically in 1864 at only eight months old. R.H. died in 1870 because of health complications that appear related to edema.
R.H.'s brother, Noah (1839-1886), also served in the Texas Brigade. The correspondence between R.H., Sallie, and Noah provides a lucid account of the Army of Northern Virginia's major campaigns and operations, including developments related to the Battles of Antietam, Chancellorsville, Gettysburg, and Chickamauga.
Garrett Scott, Sallie Scott's brother, died in action at the Battle of Antietam September 17, 1862 while serving in the Texas Brigade. His letters from the early years of the war offer yet another perspective of campaign and camp life.
R.H. and Sallie's daughter, Barbara "Belle" Bassett (1865-1958), married William Mason Blackley (1863-1898) in 1884 and lived in Staunton, Virginia before moving to Washington, D.C. Research suggests they only had one child, Belle Blackley (1890-1967), whom never married and lived out her life in Washington, D.C. However, an 1888 letter contained in this collection written by Ida Carter, the Blackley's "Black Mamy," is addressed to a Col. Bassett Blackley, in care of W. M. Blackley. Carter begins the letter "Dear Little Bassett." This letter seems to suggest that the Blackleys did in fact have another child, Bassett Blackley, prior to Belle. If that is the case, Bassett Blackley may have died in childhood.
The bulk of the twentieth-century material concerns William's nephew, Charles "Chas" Blackley Sr. (1909-1999), his wife Catherine Matthews Blackley (1914-2010), and their son and daughter-in-law Charles "Chuck" Phillips (b. 1951) and Patricia Fry Blackley (b. 1952).
Charles "Chas" Phillips Blackley Sr. was born in Staunton, Virginia in 1909. His parents died from the Spanish Flu when he was 10. Their deaths required Chas and his sister Mary Gilkeson Blackley to move in with their aunt, Fannie Blackley Cushing in Staunton. These materials cover his travels throughout the Pacific and Asia aboard a "tramp steamer" with boyhood friend, George Earman in 1930, his 1927-1929 military training in the little discussed Citizens Military Training Camps (CMTC), time at the Virginia Military Institute (VMI), his 1934 travels in Europe, World War II military service, and ownership and operation of WSVA, the first radio station in Harrisonburg, Virginia. Chas sold his share in WSVA and moved to Staunton, Virginia where he started the WTON radio station. Beyond his official jobs, Chas spent much of the early 1930s as an amateur playwright and author. Chas and Catherine Matthews were married in 1938.
While traveling Europe via train in 1934, Chas met David Kahn, a young Presbyterian judge of Indian descent. They would become lifelong friends. Mr. Kahn went on to become a governor of an Indian province under British rule and later head the Department of Sanitation for Calcutta. He and his wife visited their children, who had moved to the United States, and Mr. and Mrs. Blackley often until his health would not allow it. Evidence of their lifelong friendship can be found most clearly in this collection's correspondence and photographs.
Chas' WWII experience saw him drafted at age 35 and shipped to Camp Crowder, Missouri for training. He would eventually be transferred to Washington, D.C. where he worked as a private in the basement of the Pentagon. According this son, his superiors frequently called him upstairs to request autographed photos of American Broadcasting Company (ABC) celebrities. He was able to oblige them because of WSVA's status as an ABC affiliate.
Catherine Matthews Blackley was originally from Cambridge, Maryland and came to the Shenandoah Valley to attend the State Teacher's College at Harrisonburg (now James Madison University). She graduated in 1935 with a degree in home economics. For a short time she taught in Norfolk, Virginia before marrying Chas Blackley in 1938 and buying a home on Port Republic Road in Harrisonburg. After Chas was drafted and shipped to Camp Crowder, Mrs. Blackley traveled to Neosho, Missouri to be with her husband. While in Missouri, she volunteered with the Red Cross to help care for wounded soldiers. She continued this service after Mr. Blackley was transferred to Washington, D.C. After the war, they returned to the Valley and Catherine became a member of the Staunton School Board and was very active in volunteer work.
Charles "Chuck" Phillips Blackley Jr. was a professional engineer and graduate of Virginia Tech. He provided services in Virginia, West Virginia, and Maryland. Chuck married Patricia Fry in 1971. At the time he sold his office it was the largest engineering company in the region outside of Richmond, Roanoke, and Northern Virginia.
Patricia Fry Blackley graduated from James Madison University in 1987 and became a licensed real estate appraiser. After Chuck stepped away from his engineering office he teamed up with his wife and the couple became full-time photographers and writers. Their work can be found in hundreds of magazines, books, and calendars.
Scope and Content
The Blackley Family Papers, 1830-2016, consists of hundreds of letters that span from 1830 to 2011; diaries; official United States, Confederate, and Texas documents; literary works; newspaper clippings; postcards; ephemera; and photographs. These papers document the related Scott, Bassett, Blackley, Hoge, Matthews, and Nix families of Texas and Staunton, Virginia.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in five series:
Series 1: Correspondence 1830-2011 Series 2: Personal Papers, 1857-2016 Series 3: Ephemera, 1856-2004 Series 4: Photographs, ca.1861-1989 Series 5: Scrapbooks, 1862-1931
Series 1 is arranged chronologically by the individual who penned the letters with some overlap of dates for those individuals that require multiple folders.
Series 2 is arranged chronologically by individual and with items being authored by or specifically connected to the individuals.
Series 3 is arranged chronologically.
Series 4 is arranged chronologically by individual or groups of photos as they were found. They are described at the folder level.
Series 5 is arranged chronologically.
Related Material
Charles C. Phillips Civil War Papers. MS 0327. Virginia Military Institute Archives.
Murr, Erika, L., ed., A Rebel Wife in Texas: The Diary and Letters of Elizabeth Scott Neblett, 1852-1864. Baton Rouge: Louisiana State University Press, 2001.
Lizzie Scott Neblett Papers, 1848-1935, Dolph Briscoe Center for American History, The University of Texas at Austin.
Yourself and family are invited to attend the feast of Mondamin corn festival. n.p.: Staunton, Va.: J. Harry Drechsler, pr., [1890], 1890. JAMES MADISON UNIV's Catalog, EBSCOhost (accessed May 2, 2017).
Separated Material
All published monographs have been cataloged individually and placed in Special Collections' rare book collection. Catherine Matthews Blackley's Schooma'am yearbooks were removed and housed with the yearbook collection. They are retained due to heavy annotations.
Bibliography
Murr, Erika, L., ed., A Rebel Wife in Texas: The Diary and Letters of Elizabeth Scott Neblett, 1852-1864. Baton Rouge: Louisiana State University Press, 2001.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Blackley, Chuck; Blackley, Pat; Confederate States of America. Army. Texas Brigade; United States. War Department. Citizens' Military Training Camps; State Teachers College at Harrisonburg (Harrisonburg, Va.) -- Students; Virginia Military Institute -- Students; Military training camps -- United States; World War, 1939-1945; Radio stations -- Virginia -- Harrisonburg; Radio stations -- Virginia -- Staunton; Photography; Travel -- 20th century; Staunton (Va.) -- History -- 19th century; Staunton (Va.) -- History -- 20th century; Staunton (Va.) -- History -- 21st century; Virginia -- Genealogy; Texas -- Genealogy; Texas -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Campaigns; Augusta County (Va.) -- Social life and customs -- 19th century; Augusta County (Va.) -- Social life and customs -- 20th century; Augusta County (Va.) -- Social life and customs -- 21st century; Augusta County (Va.) -- History -- 19th century; Augusta County (Va.) -- History -- 20th century; Augusta County (Va.) -- History -- 21st century; Virginia Polytechnic Institute -- Students
Genre and Form Terms:
Letters (correspondence); Photographs; Diaries; Scrapbooks; Printed Ephemera; Drafts (documents); Pamphlets; Brochures; Scripts (documents); Newspaper clippings; Maps (documents); Color patches (military patches); Certificates; Diplomas; Postcards
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1830-2011
  Scope and Content
  Series 1: Correspondence, 1830-2011, is comprised of more than 300 individual letters with the majority of the earlier ones involve Sarah "Sallie" Scott Bassett and/or her husband R.H. Bassett. Together their combined correspondence comprise eight folders and spans the years 1850-1913.
  These letters cover the years of the American Civil War and shed light on how the conflict affected their lives. In addition to letters from Captain R.H. Bassett, there are dozens of notes written home to Sallie from her brother Garrett Scott, brother-in-law Noah Bassett, and her cousin John Nix. All of these men spent time serving in the 4th Texas Regiment of the famed Texas Brigade. While their letters contain minimal military focused discussions, they do highlight camp life, personal struggles of being separated from each other, personal and public incidents, and family news. The military discussion is really limited to mention of the dead and wounded from battles and engagements. However, R.H. does write a letter to Sallie as he arrives on the battlefield at Gettysburg. He expresses excitement to build off the Confederates successes that afternoon. Battles and engagements discussed include Antietam (September 17, 1862), Chancellorsville (April 30 to May 6, 1863), Gettysburg (July 1-3, 1863), and Chickamauga (September 18–20, 1863).
  Lizzie Scott Neblett was the older sister of Sallie Bassett and many letters between the sisters not previously examined, both before and after the American Civil War, can be found within this collection. Their letters shed light on relationship struggles, farm life, local news, and family connections.
  While few in number, the surviving letters of Lizzie and Sallie's father, James Scott, provide significant insight into Texas prior to its in 1846. In the first, James writes his wife, Sarah, from the convention in Austin, Texas, where the debates about joining the United States were taking place. He offers few specifics as "Nothing in which you would take any interest has occurred here and therefore I will not say anything about the proceedings…" In second of these letters, James is writing to a Colonel B. Rush Wallace and gets far more political in discussion and tone. He talks at length about concern over the merits of becoming Whig or Democrat once they are thrust into the existing political climate of their new nation.
  Of particular interest is an 1888 letter written by Ida Carter, presumably William M. and Belle Bassett Blackley's "Black Mamy," is addressed to a Col. Bassett Blackley, in care of W. M. Blackley. Carter begins the letter "Dear Little Bassett." This letter seems to suggest that the Blackleys did in fact have another child, Bassett Blackley, prior to Belle. If that is the case, Bassett Blackley may have died in childhood.
  Of the twentieth-century correspondence, most of it was sent or received by Chas Blackley. While his letters span most of the century, the bulk are centered between the years 1930-1944. The letters that Chas Blackley wrote while visiting Europe in 1934 are of particular interest due to the changing political climate with the rise of the Nazis in Germany. Through his correspondence, diaries, and photographs there is an opportunity to see an American view of this transformative time. In one letter to his sister, Mary, dated August 21, Chas Blackley writes of the hanging of Nazis in Vienna, Austria for a failed coup that took place mere weeks before his arrival and that it "has retarded history making considerably." He also spoke of the Heimwehr, the home guard, patrolling the streets with their rifles and "keeping a sharp to windward."
  - Grandfather Lane, 1830 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - James Scott, 1845-1856 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sallie Scott, 1851-2858 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Event Invitations (folder 1 of 2), 1856-1888, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Event Invitations (folder 2 of 2), 1856-1888, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hawthorn, 1857-1858, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alice Scott, 1857, 1861, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amanda B. White, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - R.H. Bassett, 1858-1862 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sallie Scott, 1858-1860 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Garret Scott, 1859-1862 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - John L. Nix, 1861-1863 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sallie Scott, 1861-1865 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Wedding Invitations (folder 1 of 3), 1861-1894,1938,1971,undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Wedding Invitations (folder 2 of 3), 1861-1894,1938,1971,undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Wedding Invitations (folder 3 of 3), 1861-1894,1938,1971,undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - John H. Fanthorpe, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - J. Roishin, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - JNO Lovejoy, 1900-1904 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - JN Scott, 1903-1908 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lizzie Neblett, 1903-1915 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - JNO Lovejoy, 1904-1909 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Marion Fry, 1907-1922 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Nora Boylor Fry, 1907-1921 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - E.F. Phillips, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Legal Correspondence to JNO Lovejoy, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. L.M. Sherrard, 1908-1909 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sallie Scott, 1910-1913, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bettie "Lizzie" Neblett, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Lonnie Bassett, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chas Blackley, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chas Blackley, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chas Blackley, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chas Blackley, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chas Blackley, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Annie Funkhauser, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mrs. Richard Ker, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Chas Blackley, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - R.H. Bassett, 1858-1862 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Noah Bassett, 1862-1864 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Empty Envelopes, 1862-1969, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - R.H. Bassett, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - G.M. Patrick, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - R.H. Bassett, 1863-1864, 1867, 1870 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence concerning death of son Robert Bassett, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - J.E. Carver, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - John Q. Yarborough, 1868, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - J.L. McCormick, 1869 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - G. Robinson, 1870 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Margaret Hoge Blackley, 1871 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - R.I. Teel, 1873 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Belle Bassett Blackley, 1877-1912, 1957, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - R.P. Halliburton, 1878 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mary Marie Young and Nellie Thatcher, 1879 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bettie A. Halliburton, 1880, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - John Halliburton, 1883 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Wedding Regrets for Belle and Wm Blackley, 1884 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Miss Florence Satterwhite, 1884 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Grandpa, 1885 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - J.L. Gray, 1886 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Ida Carter ("Black Mamy"), 1888 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - James H. Blackley, 1888, 1895-1898, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Carrol, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1891-1937, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Grandmother Bassett, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Jesse L. Henry, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - G.L. Scott, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - William M. Blackley, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Wm. Alsobrook, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Jesse, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - W. Neblett, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Mrs. Richard Ker, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Chas Blackley, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chas Blackley, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. Richard Ker, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chas Blackley, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 1 of 3), 1930 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 2 of 3), 1930 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 3 of 3), 1930 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chas Blackley, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript rejection letters, Chas Blackley, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chas Blackley, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Mary Blackley, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Catherine Blackley, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chas Blackley, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Mary Blackley, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 1 of 3), 1934 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 2 of 3), 1934 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 3 of 3), 1934 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Chas Blackley, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Catherine Matthews, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Legal Correspondence related to WSVA with Attorney Lavenstein, 1935-1937 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - WSVA, 1935-1938, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chas Blackley, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence related to WSVA with Attorney Lavenstein, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Kidnapping Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1936-1937, 1970, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 1 of 2), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 2 of 2), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 1 of 4), 1938 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 2 of 4), 1938 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 3 of 4), 1938 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 4 of 4), 1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chas Blackley, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chas Blackley, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chas Blackley, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Chas Blackley, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 1 of 2), 1944 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Chas Blackley (folder 2 of 2), 1944 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chas Blackley, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Chas Blackley, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Congratulatory Letters Regarding the Births of Children, 1947, 1951, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Chas Blackley, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Chas Blackley, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Chas Blackley, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Chas Blackley, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Chas Blackley, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Chas Blackley, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Chas Blackley, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Chas Blackley, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Chas Blackley, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mary Taylor, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chas Blackley, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Thank you Letter from White House and President Eisenhower, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Chas Blackley, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chas Blackley, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Chas Blackley, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chas Blackley, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Mary Taylor, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Chas Blackley, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Mary Taylor, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Chas Blackley, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Mary Taylor, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Chas Blackley, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Chas Blackley, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Patricia Blackley, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Chas Blackley, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Chas Blackley, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Chas Blackley, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Chas Blackley, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Chas Blackley, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Patricia Blackley, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Chuck Blackley, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 42)